Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- Theme Files, 1969-2002; 1969 2002; 15 linear feet
  - Spay/Neuter; Paws, Toronto Humane Society, Canada, 1987, 1989 (Box 6.016, Folder 8)
  - San Mateo County; Peninsula Humane Society, 1990s (Box 6.017, Folder 1)
  - Sled Dogs, 1991-1992 (Box 6.017, Folder 2)
  - Slaughter House: Best and Donovan packing house equipment catalog, 1971 (Box 6.022, Folder 4)
  - Slaughter house: techniques, 1970-1972 (Box 6.022, Folder 5)
  - Slaughter house: statistics, locations, legislation, 1968-1974 (Box 6.022, Folder 6)
  - Simon and Goodman Picture Company, 1989-1991 (Box 6.017, Folder 3)
  - Spanish / English Literature, circa 1990 (Box 6.017, Folder 4)
  - Spanish / English Literature, circa 1990 (Box 6.017, Folder 5)
  - St. Hubert's Giralsda - NJ, 1992-1993 (Box 6.017, Folder 6)
  - "Socks" Clinton - The First Cat, 1992-1993 (Box 6.017, Folder 7)
  - State Anti-Cruelty Statutes - Texas, 1991 (Box 6.017, Folder 8)
  - The State of the Movement, 1990 Spring (Box 6.017, Folder 9)
  - Stephen F. Sundlof, DVM, 1989 (Box 6.017, Folder 10)
  - Subway Dog - Token, 1991 (Box 6.017, Folder 11)
  - Summit For The Animals, 1991 (Box 6.017, Folder 12)
  - Surveys - Animal rights, 1991 (Box 6.017, Folder 13)
  - Swans, 1990 January 21 (Box 6.017, Folder 14)
  - Ta-Too-A-Pet - Julie Moscove, 1980s (Box 6.017, Folder 15)
  - Television Shows / Transcripts, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.017, Folder 16)
  - Thanksgiving - Holiday Vegetarian, 1980s (Box 6.017, Folder 17)
  - Timmy the Gorilla, 1992 (Box 6.018, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.018, Folder 2)
  - Turtles, 1990 (Box 6.018, Folder 3)
  - Trutt, Fran - U.S. Surgical, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.018, Folder 4)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1970s (Box 6.018, Folder 5)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1960s-1990s (Box 6.018, Folder 6)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1960s-1970s (Box 6.018, Folder 7)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1973-1974 (Box 6.018, Folder 8)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1973 (Box 6.018, Folder 9)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1985 (Box 6.018, Folder 10)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1973 (Box 6.018, Folder 11)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1972 (Box 6.018, Folder 12)
  - UAA - United Action for Animals, 1992 (Box 6.018, Folder 13)
  - UKP - United Kingdom Parliament, 1960s-1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 1)
  - Vegetarian Organizations, 1970s-1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 2)
  - UNAR - United Nations Animal Rights Club, 1970s-1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 2)
  - Veterinarians (AVAR) NY, NJ, CT, 1992 January 13 (Box 6.019, Folder 3)
  - The Unicorn, 1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 3)
  - Unti, Bernard, Humanitarian Books, 1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 4)
  - USDA, 1976 (Box 6.019, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Government - Federal Laws, 1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 6)
  - UXSC - United States Signal Corp, 1981 (Box 6.019, Folder 7)
  - Vegetarian Education Network, 1980s (Box 6.019, Folder 8)
  - Vegetarian Etiquette, 1991 (Box 6.019, Folder 9)
  - Vegetarian Resource Group, 1991 (Box 6.019, Folder 10)
  - Vegetarian Restaurants, 1991 (Box 6.019, Folder 11)
  - Vegetarianism, 1990s (Box 6.02, Folder 1)
  - Veterinary Supply Catalogs, circa 1980 (Box 6.02, Folder 6)
  - Vietnamese / English Literature, circa 1980 (Box 6.02, Folder 7)
  - Violence Toward Children, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.02, Folder 8)
  - Voice of the Trees, 1991 Fall (Box 6.02, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 6.02, Folder 10)
  - Whales, 1990 (Box 6.02, Folder 11)
  - Weisman, Frederick - Films: Primate, Meat, Racetrack, 1970s-1980s (Box 6.02, Folder 12)
  - Who Gets the Money, 1989 (Box 6.02, Folder 13)
  - Wildlife Biology - Dr. Jay R. Kirkpatrick, 1990s (Box 6.02, Folder 14)
  - Wildlife Control and Rehabilitation, Volunteers for Wildlife L.I.N.Y., 1990s (Box 6.021, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife Rehabilitation Today, 1990s (Box 6.021, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife - Endangered, 1990s (Box 6.021, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife - Saviors or Sellouts, 1988 (Box 6.021, Folder 4)
  - Wolf - Hybrids, 1991-1992 (Box 6.021, Folder 5)
  - World Charter of Students, 1991 March 20 (Box 6.021, Folder 6)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 1988, 1992 (Box 6.021, Folder 7)
  - Zoos - Adoption Programs, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.021, Folder 8)
  - Zoos - Aquariums, 1980s-1990s (Box 6.021, Folder 9)
  - Zoospaper, 1991 January (Box 6.021, Folder 10)
  - Animal Agriculture: Chickens: Broilers, 1989-1992 (Box 6-022, Folder 1)
  - Animal Agriculture: Chickens: Disease: Salmonella, 1986-1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 2)
  - Animal Agriculture: Chickens: Egg Layers, 1987-1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 3)
  - Animal Agriculture: Drug Use, 1987 (Box 6-022, Folder 4)
  - Animal Agriculture: Game Animals, 1987-1992 (Box 6-022, Folder 5)
  - Animal Agriculture: Goats, 1990 (Box 6-022, Folder 6)
  - Animal Agriculture: Horses, 1991-1992 (Box 6-022, Folder 7)
  - Animal Agriculture: Key Statistics, 1990-1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 8)
  - Animal Agriculture: Pigs, 1981-1995 (Box 6-022, Folder 9)
  - Animal Agriculture: Pro-Farming Literature, circa, 1990 (Box 6-022, Folder 10)
  - Animal Agriculture: Research, 1990 (Box 6-022, Folder 11)
  - Animal Agriculture: Sheep, 1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 12)
  - Animal Agriculture: Slaughterhouses, 1988-1990 (Box 6-022, Folder 13)
  - Animal Agriculture: Turkeys, 1987 (Box 6-022, Folder 14)
  - Dissection, 1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 15)
  - Dissection: Humane Education, 1987-1991 (Box 6-022, Folder 16)
  - Earth First! Journal, 1998 (incomplete) (Box 6-022, Folder 17)
  - Earth First! Journal, 1993-1997 (incomplete) (Box 6.023, Folder 1)
  - Earth First! Journal, 1989-1990 (incomplete) (Box 6.023, Folder 2)
  - Jean McClure Kelty, "Once Theirs Alone", 1972 (Box 6.023, Folder 3)
  - Fish: Contamination, 1990-1992 (Box 6.023, Folder 4)
  - Fish: Endangered, 1983-1992 (Box 6.023, Folder 5)
  - Fish: Endangered: Tallico Dam (TN), 1978-1980 (Box 6.023, Folder 6)
  - Fish: Hatcheries/Fisheries, 1990-1992 (Box 6.023, Folder 7)
  - Fish: Type: Bass, 1987-1992 (Box 6.023, Folder 8)
  - Fish: Type: Salmon, 1989-1995 (Box 6.023, Folder 9)
  - Fish: Type: Trout, 1988-1995 (Box 6.024, Folder 1)
  - Fish: Type: Tuna, 1978-1991 (Box 6.024, Folder 2)
  - Fishing: Arkansas, 1988-1993 (Box 6.024, Folder 3)
  - Fishing: California, 1990-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 4)
  - Fishing: Colorado, 1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 5)
  - Fishing: Florida, 1990-1993 (Box 6.024, Folder 6)
  - Fishing: Georgia, 1990 (Box 6.024, Folder 7)
  - Fishing: Hawaii, 1991 (Box 6.024, Folder 8)
  - Fishing: Maine, 1990 (Box 6.024, Folder 9)
  - Fishing: Maryland, 1990-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 10)
  - Fishing: Michigan, 1991-1993 (Box 6.024, Folder 11)
  - Fishing: New York, 1991-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 12)
  - Fishing: North Dakota, 1991 (Box 6.024, Folder 13)
  - Fishing: Pennsylvania, 1991-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 14)
  - Fishing: Texas, 1991 (Box 6.024, Folder 15)
  - Fishing: Vermont, 1988-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 16)
  - Fishing: Virginia, 1991 (Box 6.024, Folder 17)
  - Fishing: Washington, 1992-1993 (Box 6.024, Folder 18)
  - Fishing: Wyoming, 1995 (Box 6.024, Folder 19)
  - March for the Animals, Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 6.024, Folder 20)
  - Pollution Hunting Wildlife (Air, Acid Rain, Atmospheric), 1987-1992 (Box 6.024, Folder 21)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife(Land), 1980-1995 (Box 6.024, Folder 22)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife (Water-Miscellaneous), 1985-1989 (Box 6.024, Folder 23)
  - Pollution Hurting Wildlife (Water Oil), 1981-1990 (Box 6.025, Folder 1)
  - Vivisection: Ethics: Animal Experimentation, 1988-1991 (Box 6.025, Folder 2)
  - Vivisection: Ethics: Animal Dog Dealing, 1989-1991 (Box 6.025, Folder 3)
  - Vivisection: Fetal Research, 1990-1991 (Box 6.025, Folder 4)
  - Vivisection: General Motors Crash Tests, 1991-1992 (Box 6.025, Folder 5)
  - Vivisection: Genetic Engineering, 1987-1990 (Box 6.025, Folder 6)
  - Vivisection: Head Injury, 1990-1991 (Box 6.025, Folder 7)
  - Vivisection: Heart, 1989-1990 (Box 6.025, Folder 8)
  - Vivisection: Lab Raids, 1990-1993 (Box 6.025, Folder 9)
  - Vivisection: Military, 1990-1992 (Box 6.025, Folder 10)
  - Vivisection: Organ Transplant, 1992 (Box 6.025, Folder 11)
  - Vivisection: Pro-Animal, Anti-Vivisection, 1989-1994 (Box 6.025, Folder 12)
  - Vivisection: Product Testing Cruelty Free Products, 1990-1994 (Box 6.026, Folder 1)
  - Vivisection: Product Testing Draize Test, 1987-1990 (Box 6.026, Folder 2)
  - Vivisection: Proposed Bills, Legislation and Rulings, 1989-1993 (Box 6.026, Folder 3)
  - Vivisection: Scientific Fraud, 1990-1993 (Box 6.026, Folder 4)
  - Vivisection: Silver Spring Monkeys, 1990-1992 (Box 6.026, Folder 5)
  - Vivisection: Stress, 1989-1990 (Box 6.026, Folder 6)
  - Vivisection: Stroke, 1990-1991 (Box 6.026, Folder 7)
  - Vivisector's Defense, 1989-1990 (Box 6.026, Folder 8)
  - Vivisection: Wildlife, 1990-1991 (Box 6.026, Folder 9)
  - Vegetarian Journal, 1993-1996 (Box 6.026, Folder 10)
  - Wildlife: Acid Rain, 1979-1986 and undated (Box 6.026, Folder 11)
  - Wildlife: Arboretum Deer Kill, 1987-1989 (Box 6.026, Folder 12)
  - Wildlife: Attacks, 1987-1990 and undated (Box 6.026, Folder 13)
  - Wildlife: Bears, 1985-1986 (Box 6.026, Folder 14)
  - Wildlife: Big Game Hunting, 1984-1987 (Box 6.026, Folder 15)
  - Wildlife: Captive Wildlife, 1985-1993 and undated (Box 6.026, Folder 16)
  - Wildlife: Damage, 1979-1989 and undated (Box 6.026, Folder 17)
  - Wildlife: Deer Hunting, General, 1963, 1983-1990 (Box 6.027, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife: Effectiveness of Wildlife Warning Reflectors, 1983-1986 (Box 6.027, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife: Endangered Species, 1975-1990 (Box 6.027, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife: Environmental Damage, 1983-1990 and undated (Box 6.027, Box 4)
  - Wildlife: Environmental Education, 1987 and undated (Box 6.027, Folder 5)
  - Wildlife: Environmental Impact, 1982-1990 (Box 6.027, Folder 6)
  - Wildlife: Fur Industry, 1984-1993 and undated (Box 6.027, Folder 7)
  - Wildlife: Fur Ranchers and Dealers, 1983-1990 and undated (Box 6.027, Folder 8)
  - Wildlife: General Information, 1984-1990 and undated (Box 6.027, Folder 9)
  - Wildlife: Humane Pest Control, undated (Box 6.027, Folder 10)
  - Wildlife: Hunting Overview, 1985-1990 and undated (Box 6.027, Folder 11)
  - Wildlife: Hunting Techniques, 1987 (Box 6.027, Folder 12)
  - Wildlife: The Niche, Fall and Winter 1987 (Box 6.027, Folder 13)
  - Wildlife: Popualtion Control, 1970-1990 (Box 6.027, Folder 14)
  - Wildlife: Rainforests, 1984-1987 (Box 6.027, Folder 15)
  - Wildlife: Wisconsin Department of Natural Resources Conservation Congress (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1990 (Box 6.027, Folder 16)
  - Wildlife: Wisconsin Department of Natural Resources Conservation Congress (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1990 (Box 2.028, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife: Zoos, 1987 (Box 6.028, Folder 2)
  - Zoo Animals: Use in Research, undated (Box 6.028, Folder 3)
  - Wool: General/Miscellaneous, 1990-1995 (Box 6.028, Folder 4)
  - Zoos: Canada, 1989 (Box 6.028, Folder 5)
  - Zoos: Entertainment/Foreign, 1991-1992 (Box 6.028, Folder 6)
  - Zoos: Foreign: United Kingdom, 1990-1992 (Box 6.028, Folder 7)
  - Zoos: Problems with Captive Breedking/Reintroduction, 1991 (Box 6.028, Folder 8)
  - "Painful Experiments": Final Manuscript by Dallas Pratt, undated (Box 6.028, Folder 9)
  - Traps and Trapping, 1977 (Box 6.028, Folder 11)
- Film Literature, 1956-1998; 1956 1998; 12.76 linear feet
  The Film Literature series documents the Argus Archives business transactions and humane education film resource catalogs used in acquiring films by rental or purchase. These films were then previewed by Argus Archives staff to determine if they would be shown at the Argus Archives biannual humane education film presentations. Types of organizations that supplied these catalogs include, but are not limited to, film production companies, television broadcasting companies, humane organizations, local and national governments, universities, and corporations. This series has been physically maintained in its original order, alphabetically by organization name. However, folders are listed here showing Argus Archives organizational material before the organization catalogs.
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Films for Humane Education, 1977-1980 (Box 7.015, Folder 13)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, AP Certificate of Copyright registration for "Alternatives to pain in Experiments on Animals,", 1980-1981 (Box 7.015, Folder 14)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Legislation and other materials related to registration, 1970s-1980 (Box 7.015, Folder 15)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright,Tamp;T;Famp;F, Certificate Registration of a Claim to Copyright for "Furs and Fashion - Traps and Trapping, 1971, 1977 (Box 7.015, Folder 16)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, PEOA, Certificate Registration of a Claim to Copyright for "Painful Experiments on Animals,", 1976 June 18 (Box 7.015, Folder 17)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Slaughter Report, Certificate of copyright registration for "Animals Into Meat: A Report On The Pre-Slaughter of Livestock,", 1971 April 22 (Box 7.015, Folder 18)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Reprints: requests for copyright permissions to quote., 1970s-1980 (Box 7.015, Folder 19)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Information: Motion Picture Agreement Information, 1989 (Box 7.015, Folder 20)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Library of Congress: Bill receipts from the Cataloging Distribution Service Division, correspondence relating to the establishment of an account, catalog card brochure, 1970s, 1983 (Box 7.015, Folder 21)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Library of Congress, AP: Request for Library of Congress Catalog Card Number for "Alternatives to Pain In Experiments on Animals,", 1983 October 26 (Box 7.015, Folder 22)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Library of Congress, AP: Request for Library of Congress Catalog Card Number for "Traps and Trapping; Furs and Fashion" and catalog cards, 1980 Spring (Box 7.015, Folder 23)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Library of Congress, AP: Request for Library of Congress Catalog Card Number for "Films for Humane Education" and catalog cards, 1977 May (Box 7.015, Folder 24)
  - AA - Argus Archives: Copyright, Library of Congress, AP: Request for Library of Congress Catalog Card Number for "Painful experiments on Animals" and catalog cards, 1979 March 28 (Box 7.015, Folder 25)
  - Film Literature - printed matter relating to Humane education, 1980s-1990s (Box 7.001, Folder 1)
  - ABC - TV, 1981 June 22 (Box 7.001, Folder 2)
  - AFVA - American Film and Video Association, 1988 September (Box 7.001, Folder 3)
  - Adelphi Productions, 1980s (Box 7.001, Folder 4)
  - AIMS Instructional Media, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.001, Folder 5)
  - Alpo, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.001, Folder 6)
  - AAAS - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1977 (Box 7.001, Folder 7)
  - AALAS - American Association for Laboratory Animal Science, 1970s (Box 7.001, Folder 8)
  - American Cyanamid Co., Surgical Film Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 7.001, Folder 9)
  - American Educational Films, 1970s (Box 7.001, Folder 10)
  - Animal Welfare Institute, 1975, 1981 (Box 7.001, Folder 11)
  - American Fund For Alternatives To Animal Research, 1983-1985 (Box 7.001, Folder 12)
  - The American Hereford Association, 1977 (Box 7.001, Folder 13)
  - The American Humane Association, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.001, Folder 14)
  - AHES - American Humane Education Society, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.001, Folder 15)
  - American Psychological Association, 1978 (Box 7.001, Folder 16)
  - American Sheep Producers, Inc., 1977 (Box 7.001, Folder 17)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1970s (Box 7.001, Folder 18)
  - Anchor Laboratories, 1977, 1980 (Box 7.001, Folder 19)
  - Animal Kind - Survival Anglia Limited, 1985 (Box 7.001, Folder 20)
  - API - Animal Protection Institute, 1977 (Box 7.001, Folder 21)
  - Animals Friend Film, Crystal Rogers, 1977 June (Box 7.001, Folder 22)
  - Argentine Embassy, 1977 January 4 (Box 7.001, Folder 23)
  - Arthur Mokin Productions, 1970s (Box 7.001, Folder 24)
  - Associated Press, 1987 (Box 7.001, Folder 25)
  - Association Films, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 7.002, Folder 1)
  - Association Sterling Films, 1976-1977 (Box 7.002, Folder 2)
  - Association For The Protection of Fur Bearing Animals, 1978 (Box 7.002, Folder 3)
  - AVNA Media, Audio Visual Narrative Arts, Inc., 1986 (Box 7.002, Folder 4)
  - AVNA Media, Audio Visual Narrative Arts, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 7.002, Folder 5)
  - Australian Information Service, Film Australia, circa 1978 (Box 7.002, Folder 6)
  - Avalon Daggett Productions, 1974 November 1 (Box 7.002, Folder 7)
  - barr films, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.002, Folder 8)
  - Beacon Films, 1981 (Box 7.002, Folder 9)
  - Beauty Without Cruelty, 1971 (Box 7.002, Folder 10)
  - Benchmark Films, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 7.002, Folder 11)
  - Best Films, circa 1978 (Box 7.002, Folder 12)
  - BFA Educational Media, A division of CBS, Inc., 1970s-1980s (Box 7.002, Folder 13)
  - Biology Media, 1983 Spring (Box 7.002, Folder 14)
  - Biosphere Films - Dolphins, 1980s-1990s (Box 7.002, Folder 15)
  - Bodacious Films, circa 1980 (Box 7.002, Folder 16)
  - Bosustow productions, 1979 (Box 7.002, Folder 17)
  - Boulder Humane Society, Boulder CO, 1978-1979 (Box 7.002, Folder 18)
  - Bowling Green Films, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 7.002, Folder 19)
  - Brauer Productions, 1987-1988 (Box 7.002, Folder 20)
  - Britannica Films, 1984-1985 (Box 7.002, Folder 21)
  - British Film Institute, 1970s (Box 7.003, Folder 1)
  - British Films Limited, circa 1976 (Box 7.003, Folder 2)
  - British Ind. and Scientific Association, 1975 March 11 (Box 7.003, Folder 3)
  - Browning Film Library, 1977 September 20 (Box 7.003, Folder 4)
  - Bullfrog Films, Inc., 1980s-1990s (Box 7.003, Folder 5)
  - Bunkelman and Leggett Films, 1979 July 17 (Box 7.003, Folder 6)
  - CBS News, 1975, 1981 (Box 7.003, Folder 7)
  - CMG Information Services, 1987 (Box 7.003, Folder 8)
  - Cactus Clyde Distributions, 1977 March 22 (Box 7.003, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Association for Humane Trapping, 1979 December 6 (Box 7.003, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Film Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 7.003, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Filmmakers Distribution Centre, 1981 (Box 7.003, Folder 12)
  - Carousel Films, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 7.003, Folder 13)
  - Center For Humanities, 1988 (Box 7.003, Folder 14)
  - Center For Understanding Media, 1974 Winter (Box 7.003, Folder 15)
  - Centre Productions, 1987 (Box 7.003, Folder 16)
  - Centron Films, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.003, Folder 17)
  - Chemagro, Division of Baychem Corporation Advertising Section, 1977 January 4 (Box 7.003, Folder 18)
  - Charles Clark Co., Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 7.003, Folder 19)
  - Churchill Films, 1970s- 1990s (Box 7.004, Folder 1)
  - CINE Information, circa 1978 (Box 7.004, Folder 2)
  - Cinema 5, 1979 (Box 7.004, Folder 3)
  - Cinema Incorporated, 1978 (Box 7.004, Folder 4)
  - Communications Park Publishing Group, 1984 July 24 (Box 7.004, Folder 5)
  - Community Animal Control, 1987 (Box 7.004, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University, 1983-1984 (Box 7.004, Folder 7)
  - Coronet Films, 1980s (Box 7.004, Folder 8)
  - Counterpoint Films, circa 1980 (Box 7.004, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Craven Film Corporation, 1980 (Box 7.004, Folder 10)
  - CRM/McGraw-Hill, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.004, Folder 11)
  - Crystal Productions, 1979-1980 (Box 7.004, Folder 12)
  - Cypress, 1982 (Box 7.004, Folder 13)
  - DeNonno Pix, Inc.: Tony de Nonno - Filmmaker, 1981 September 3 (Box 7.005, Folder 1)
  - Defenders of Wildlife, 1977 September 16 (Box 7.005, Folder 2)
  - Des Produits Audio, circa 1980 (Box 7.005, Folder 3)
  - Denoyer - Geppart Audio Visuals, 1979-1980 (Box 7.005, Folder 4)
  - Direct Cinema Ltd., 1980 (Box 7.005, Folder 5)
  - Disney - Walt Disney Educational Media Company, 1979 (Box 7.005, Folder 6)
  - Document Associates, 1977-1978 (Box 7.005, Folder 7)
  - Donars Productions, 1973 (Box 7.005, Folder 8)
  - Doubleday Media, 1974 (Box 7.005, Folder 9)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1977 (Box 7.005, Folder 10)
  - Downtown Community Television Center, circa 1978 (Box 7.005, Folder 11)
  - Ducks - Foie Gras, 1992 April 7 (Box 7.005, Folder 12)
  - EAV - Newsweek multimedia, 1980 (Box 7.005, Folder 13)
  - EAV - Educational audio visual, Inc., 1981 (Box 7.005, Folder 14)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1977-1978 (Box 7.005, Folder 15)
  - EDC - Education Development Center, 1977 July (Box 7.005, Folder 16)
  - EDC - Education Development Center, 1977 July (Box 7.005, Folder 17)
  - EDG - Education Dimensions Group, 1980-1981 (Box 7.005, Folder 18)
  - Educational Enrichment Materials - A Company of the New York Times, 1980 September 30 (Box 7.005, Folder 19)
  - Educational Images, 1980s (Box 7.005, Folder 20)
  - EFLA - Educational Film Library Association, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.005, Folder 21)
  - Educational Media Corporation, 1979 (Box 7.005, Folder 22)
  - Educators Progress Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 7.005, Folder 23)
  - Elanco Products Company, 1984 September 24 (Box 7.005, Folder 24)
  - Elliot Noyes, 1979 July 5 (Box 7.005, Folder 25)
  - EMC Corporation, 1980s (Box 7.005, Folder 26)
  - Encyclopedia Brittanica Films, 1980s (Box 7.005, Folder 27)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 7.006, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency of the United States, 1978 (Box 7.006, Folder 2)
  - Explorers Club, 1979 (Box 7.006, Folder 3)
  - Films communicators, 1987-1988 (Box 7.006, Folder 4)
  - Films Incorporated, 1984 (Box 7.006, Folder 5)
  - Filmmakers Library, 1979, 1987, 1990 (Box 7.006, Folder 6)
  - Films Incorporated Education, A division of PMI, Public Media Incorporated, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.006, Folder 7)
  - Films for Public Libraries, Learning Corporation of America, 1977 November 23 (Box 7.006, Folder 8)
  - FilmFair Communications, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.006, Folder 9)
  - FVA - Film Video Art, 1990 (Box 7.006, Folder 10)
  - Film Video - Learning Corporation of America, 1985 (Box 7.006, Folder 11)
  - Film and Video - Alfred Higgins Productions, Inc., 1987 (Box 7.006, Folder 12)
  - Florida Department of Commerce - Florida Film Library, 1970s-1980 (Box 7.006, Folder 13)
  - Florida State University Regional Film Library, circa 1980 (Box 7.006, Folder 14)
  - Flying Tomato Films / Productions, circa 1980 (Box 7.006, Folder 15)
  - Forest Service, USDA, 1978-1980 (Box 7.006, Folder 16)
  - Friends of the Sea Otter, circa 1980 (Box 7.006, Folder 17)
  - Fusion Video, circa 1975 (Box 7.006, Folder 18)
  - Gaines - Dog Research Center, 1979 (Box 7.006, Folder 19)
  - Good Shepherd Shelter, 1980 January (Box 7.006, Folder 20)
  - Graphic Curriculum, 1976-1977 (Box 7.006, Folder 21)
  - Green Mountain Post Films, 1980 Spring (Box 7.006, Folder 22)
  - University of Guelph, 1979 May (Box 7.006, Folder 23)
  - GA - Guidance Associates, 1988-1989 (Box 7.006, Folder 24)
  - Handel Films, Inc., 1976, 1978, 1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 1)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc., 1977, 1981 (Box 7.007, Folder 2)
  - Harper's Ferry Historical Association - National Park Service Films, 1979-1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 3)
  - Hartley Film Foundation, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.007, Folder 4)
  - Higgins - Alfred Higgins Film Productions, Inc., 1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 5)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1978 June 21 (Box 7.007, Folder 6)
  - Hubbard, 1979-1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 7)
  - Humane Exploration - Humane Society of the Pikes Peak Region, 1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 8)
  - Humane Paraphernalia, 1978 (Box 7.007, Folder 9)
  - HSUS - Humane Society of the United States, 1970s-1980s (Box 7.007, Folder 10)
  - University of Illinois Film Center, 1982-1984 (Box 7.007, Folder 11)
  - Indianapolis Humane Society, 1982 (Box 7.007, Folder 12)
  - Insight Films, 1977 (Box 7.007, Folder 13)
  - International Film Bureau, Inc., 1970s-1980s (Box 7.007, Folder 14)
  - International Film Foundation, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 7.007, Folder 15)